// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is cybersecurity?",
    answer: "The practice of protecting computers and the internet from bad guys",
    options: [
      "A type of computer virus",
      "A super hero who fights hackers",
      "The practice of protecting computers and the internet from bad guys",
      "A new video game"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of personal information that you should never share online?",
    answer: "Your full name",
    options: [
      "Your favorite color",
      "Your full name",
      "Your favorite cartoon character",
      "Your favorite pizza toppings"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What should you do if you receive an email or message from someone you don't know asking for your password?",
    answer: "ask a trusted adult for help",
    options: [
      "Ignore the Message",
      "Share the password with them",
      "ask a trusted adult for help",
      "tell your password is '123456' "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Why is it important to create strong passwords for your online accounts?",
    answer: "To keep your accounts safe form hackers",
    options: [
      "To make it easier for you to remember",
      "To keep your accounts safe form hackers",
      "To impress your friends",
      "To unlock special features in online games"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What should you do if you see something online that makes you feel scared, uncomfortable, or confused?",
    answer: "Tell a grow-up you trust right away",
    options: [
      "Keep it to yourself",
      "Laugh at it with your friends",
      "Tell a grow-up you trust right away",
      "Try to forget about it and move on"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of cyberbullying?",
    answer: "Sending mean messags to someone online",
    options: [
      "Sharing a funny meme with your friends",
      "Sending mean messags to someone online",
      "Asking someone toe your friend on social media site",
      "Playing an online game with your classmates"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the best way to stay safe when downloading new apps or games online?",
    answer: "Read reviews from other users",
    options: [
      "Download as many apps as you can",
      "Read reviews from other users",
      "Share your personal information with the app developers",
      "Download apps from any website you find"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does it mean to be a responsible digital citizen?",
    answer: "Being kind and respectful to others",
    options: [
      "Sharing funny videos with your friends",
      "Being kind and respectful to others",
      "ignoring messages from strangers",
      "pretending to be someone else online"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a good password?",
    answer: "123456789",
    options: [
      "Password123",
      "ilovecats",
      "123456789",
      "!Myloveis@cats"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What should you do if you accidentally click on a suspicious link or pop-up ad?",
    answer: "Tell a grown up trust and run a security scan on your device",
    options: [
      "Click on it again to see what happpens",
      "close the window and ignore it",
      "share it with your friends",
      "Tell a grown up trust and run a security scan on your device"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];